今晚，在军法署...
Tonight, on JAG...
晚上好，我是诺曼·德拉波特
Good evening, I'm Norman Delaporte.
您将看到的报告
The report you are about to see
包含有关战争和死亡的详细描述
contains graphic descriptions of war and death.
涉及到关于战争罪行的突发新闻
It involves a breaking story about war crimes
由美国海军陆战队在沙漠风暴行动期间犯下
committed by American marines during Operation Desert Storm
在科威特的埃尔巴卡尔基地
here in Kuwait at the El Bakkar compound.
指控很严重；影响很大
The accusations are serious; The repercussions, great.
您正在观看的录像是由一支海军陆战队侦察小组拍摄的
The footage you are watching was shot by a marine force
他们在沙漠风暴地面战开始前一天被派往敌后
recon team sent behind enemy lines the day before
该小组由克莱德·莫里森中士领导
the ground-war phase of Desert Storm began.
消灭三名美国人
The team was led by Sergeant Clyde Morrison.
战争罪行是由当时的二等中尉弗兰科·切法鲁发现的
To eliminate three Americans.
两天前，我在弗吉尼亚北部的家中采访了弗兰科·切法鲁，
The war crime was discovered
现在是一名海军陆战队上尉
by then-second-Lieutenant Franco Cefalu.
我的部队在侦察部队突袭两天后占领了埃尔巴卡尔
Two days ago, I interviewed Franco Cefalu,
你在五号建筑里发现了什么？
now a marine captain, at his home in northern Virginia.
三名死去的美国人，
My unit overran El Bakkar two days after the Force Recon raid.
与萨达姆·侯赛因合作的化学工程师
And what did you find in building five?
参与他的制造大规模杀伤性武器的计划
Three dead Americans,
这三个人是怎么死的？
chemical engineers working with Saddam Hussein
死于沙林毒气的影响
on his program to develop weapons of mass destruction.
那晚拍摄的视频
How did these three men die?
显示侦察部队包围了五号建筑
From the effects of sarin gas.
遭到激烈抵抗，海军陆战队向建筑物发射了
Video footage shot that night
后来被证明是沙林毒气的罐子
shows the Force Recon team surrounding building five.
录像在莫里森中士的命令下停止了
Encountering fierce resistance, the marines fired canisters
停止！停下！停下来，离开这里！
of what later proved to be sarin gas into the building.
机密情报文件显示
That's when the taping stopped
美国军方知道这些工程师在埃尔巴卡尔的存在
at Sergeant Morrison's order.
五角大楼的一位高层消息人士证实，这些人
Stop! Stop it! Stop it and get out of here!
对我们的战争努力构成了严重威胁
Classified intelligence documents indicate
海军陆战队有四人伤亡
that the American military knew of the presence
幸存者被直升机空运出去
of these engineers at El Bakkar.
理查德·福特中士是机组长和炮手
A source high up in the Pentagon confirmed that these men
中士，你撤离的海军陆战队员
posed a serious threat to our war effort.
从埃尔巴卡尔带走了沙林毒气吗？
The marines suffered four casualties.
是的，先生，莫里森中士带走了，先生
The survivors were airlifted out by helicopter.
你怎么知道的？
Sergeant Richard Ford was crew chief and gunner.
他把它放在他的子弹带里，先生
Sergeant, did the marines you evacuated
我们将在一分钟后回来，带来五角大楼的反应
from El Bakkar carry sarin gas?
Yes, sir, Sergeant Morrison did, sir.
And how do you know that?
He had it in his bandolier, sir.
We'll be back in a minute with reaction from the Pentagon.
这些指控很严重...
The charges are serious...
美国人使用化学武器杀死其他美国人
Americans using chemical weapons to kill other Americans.
好吧，我会考虑行政解雇
Well, I'll consider an administrative discharge.
今天你最多能得到三年
Three's the best you're going to get today.
-几个月？ -几年
-Months? -Years.
你一定是在开玩笑
You've got to be kidding.
哈姆，埃尔斯沃斯下士偷了一辆推土机
Harm, Petty Officer Ellsworth stole
从一个保密设施里
a bulldozer from a secured facility
并摧毁了他当地国会议员的竞选总部
and destroyed the campaign headquarters
这是一种看法
of his local congressman.
我没有时间争论
That's one way of looking at it.
我得去接那个澳大利亚交流军官
I don't have time to argue.
布朗比少校
I've got to go pick up that Australian exchange officer
-让巴德去！ -我听说布朗比很帅
Lieutenant Commander brumby.
麦可，埃尔斯沃斯下士
-Send Bud! -I hear brumby's cute.
是在发表政治声明
Mac, Petty Officer Ellsworth
国会不会批准军人的加薪
was making a political statement.
所以他的行为受到言论自由的保护？
Congress won't approve pay raises for the military.
不，但我不认为监禁能实现正义
So his actions are protected under free speech?
再想想
No, but I don't think justice is served with brig time.
感谢您在这么短的时间内见我，将军
Think again.
我很乐意来找您，女议员
Thanks for seeing me on such short notice, admiral.
我想要这次会面不被记录，AJ
I'd have been glad to come to you, congresswoman.
众议院国家安全小组委员会
I wanted this off the record, AJ
下周将举行听证会
The house national security subcommittee
我们打算查明是否有海军陆战队侦察部队
is holding hearings next week.
使用化学武器暗杀
We intend to find out whether a marine team recon force
三名为萨达姆武器计划工作的
used chemical weapons to assassinate
美国叛逃平民工程师
three renegade American civilian engineers
我昨晚见过德拉波特
working on Saddam's weapons programs.
你真的相信那个故事吗？
I saw Delaporte last night.
我认为这是有可能的
You don't actually believe that story, do you?
无论如何
I believe it's plausible.
我需要知道它是否可以证实
One way or another
五角大楼正在调查此事
I need to know if it can be substantiated.
这就像让狐狸去数鸡一样
Pentagon's looking into it.
这就是为什么我的委员会将举行会议
That like sending the fox in to count the chickens.
并向国会提交报告
And that's why my committee will hold meetings
那么，在这种情况下，女士，您需要我做什么？
and will forward a report to congress.
我希望小哈蒙·拉布海军少校被分配到我的团队
Well, in that case, ma'am, what do you need from me?
进行临时工作
I want Lieutenant Commander Rabb assigned to my staff
女士，我很乐意合作
on temporary duty.
但拉布少校的案件负担很重。我需要他
Ma'am, I'd love to cooperate
我也需要他，AJ
but Commander Rabb's caseload is full. I need him.
这是一件复杂的事情
I need him, too, AJ
这是一个复杂的话题
This is a complex subject.
很多人会撒谎
A lot of people are going to lie.
我需要一个能识别真相的人
I need to have someone who'll recognize the truth.
此外，我会欠你一个人情
Besides, I'll owe you one.
而且我一定会兑现，女士
And I have every intention of collecting, ma'am.
宣布从悉尼抵达的274航班
Announcing the arrival of flight 274 from Sydney
在20b登机口
at gate 20b.
此时我们想优先登机
At this time we'd like to pre-board
前往巴塞罗那的676航班
flight number 676 to Barcelona.
您可以通过11号登机口登机
You may board through gate 11.
保重
Be safe.
你好！我是军法署的萨拉·麦肯齐少校
Hi! I'm Major Sarah MacKenzie, JAG corp.
-什么？ -不好意思
-Sorry? -Excuse me.
不，不好意思。我在和别人说话
No, excuse me. I'm talking to someone.
我被要求在这里接你
I was asked to meet you here.
真的吗？
Really?
少校...
Major...
听着，我不在乎你和那边的朋友
Look, I don't care what kind of wager
打了什么赌。别烦我
you made with your pals over there. Leave me alone.
赌注？
Wager?
我可以带你去任何你想去的地方
I can take you anywhere you want to go.
这是个有趣的提议
Now, that's an interesting offer.
很高兴见到你，布伦比少校
It's a real pleasure to meet you, Commander Brumby.
-布伦比？ -很高兴见到你，少校
-Brumby? -The pleasure's all mine, major.
我在航班上遇到了一些朋友
I ran into some mates on the flight.
我们聊得很开心
We were gas-bagging it.
我不是布伦比少校
I'm not Commander Brumby
但我会在城里待几天
but I willbe in town for a few days.
你可以在希尔顿找到我
You can reach me at the Hilton.
好吧，你交了个朋友
Well, you made yourself a friend.
非常抱歉。嗯，萨拉·麦肯齐
I'm so sorry. Um, Sarah MacKenzie.
这是个诚实的错误
It was an honest mistake.
米克·布伦比
Mic brumby.
好吧，你想去哪儿...
Well, where would you like to go...
嗯，办公室还是酒店？
Um, office or hotel?
先去酒店，然后去办公室
Hotel, then the office.
不如直接开始工作
Might as well get straight down to the cases.
我喜欢有工作热情的人
I like a man with a hard work ethic.
当我还是个孩子的时候
When I was a kid
我从没想过我会在这个地方附近
I never dreamed I'd be anywhere near this place.
当我还是个孩子的时候，这就是我梦寐以求的
When I was a kid, it was all I dreamt about.
那么我们从哪里开始？
So where do we start?
诺曼·德拉波特
Norman Delaporte.
你真的认为这很聪明吗
You really think that's smart
考虑到我们没有所有的事实？
considering we don't have all the facts?
这正是我们要和他谈的原因
That's exactly why we're talking to him.
我通常不从记者那里获取事实
I don't usually get my facts from a reporter.
哈姆，诺曼不仅仅是个记者
Harm, Norman's not just a reporter.
他是一个机构
He's an institution.
此外，他们不会因为错误而给你皮博迪奖和普利策奖
Besides, they don't give you a peabody and a pulitzer
for being wrong.
无论如何，我认识他
Anyway, I know him.
也许这就是让我担心的原因
Maybe that's what worries me.
是谁让您接触到这个故事的，德拉波特先生？
Who put you on to this story, Mr. Delaporte?
是一个拒绝掩盖战争罪行的人...
Someone who refused to cover up a war crime...
是一个希望我
Someone who wanted me
找出那晚负责的人
to find out who was responsible
并确保这种事情不会再次发生的人
for what happened that night
and to make sure that it never happened again.
有人很忙
Someone was busy.
那么您是如何获得
So how did you get access
机密情报报告的访问权限的？
to classified intelligence reports?